{
    "id": "4766879d9fb84d23bbfb04ac003918fa",
    "title": "Sentence Linkers Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He owns a car ................................ a bike.",
            "description": "Use either as well as or and here.",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "and",
                "and as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "66e98a9e3a804c0280b97c1cf5bab887"
        },
        {
            "question": "It rained ............................... the afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8de39f8f63f447f0bab30452b7715d53"
        },
        {
            "question": "He developed a Canadian accent .............................. his stay in Canada.",
            "description": "Use during when we are talking about the whole of a period.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90b3b00d2e684c6e828d6b2d566f4323"
        },
        {
            "question": "His success is largely ............................... his hard work.",
            "description": "We do not normally use owing to after a form of be.",
            "answers": [
                "due to",
                "because of",
                "owing to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "462e08f8311b416682daa22a8661f90d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The night was ................................ dark that I could not see anything.",
            "description": "The conjunction so..that... expresses cause and effect.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65c3bebec25e4504b4990517f54d17fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Someone broke into their home .................................. they were holidaying in Venice.",
            "description": "While can show time.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a1eed4220df43c5947057d0488fd1f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He opened the garage .............................. took his things out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d931dd178f414618831e53b686b17601"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. his illness he could not attend the party.",
            "description": "All of these expressions mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "Due to",
                "Owing to",
                "Because of",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "9bc1410e12844ec496ff502c5d46e53d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was working on a new project ............................... last summer.",
            "description": "We use during when we are talking about the whole of a period. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "779e6cd423b64431a3cf7dad79bc68b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ............................... upset that she started crying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ea3258a25224d16ad5a57e734091810"
        },
        {
            "question": "I befriended a lot of Americans ................................. I was holidaying in Chicago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efdcfcdac64b42cfab9b59b142bfe7b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I befriended a lot of Americans ………………………… my holiday in Chicago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "356b1089c81945f8bd3d330c5791f003"
        }
    ]
}